https://nymox.com/privacy-policy

HomeCorporateAbout usTeamScienceResearch strategy BPHFexapotide for BPHPipelineScientific PublicationsProductsFexapotide TriflutateNicAlert®TobacAlert®InvestorsOverviewCompany PresentationStock InfoEmail AlertsCorporate GovernanceSEC FilingsAnnual ReportsNewsPress ReleasesUpcoming EventsContact
Navigation
Privacy Policy We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of information we may collect from you as a result of your visit to our website. To this end, we are committed to using our best efforts to respect your privacy. Personally Identifiable Information We collect personally identifiable information, such as names, addresses, email addresses, email messages and the like, only when voluntarily provided by you. We will not share that information with anyone else without your consent except to the extent necessary to respond to a request from you for a product, service or information. We do not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. We may use personally identifiable information in order to provide you with further information about our company and our products. User Information We also collect general information about the visitors to our web site in order to make our site more useful to you. This information can include which web pages you visited, the date and time you accessed our site, and the Internet address of the web site from which you linked to our site. We will not use this information to attempt to identify you except as part of an investigation into an unlawful attempt to “hack” or otherwise damage or gain unauthorized access to our site or Internet service. About “Cookies” Like most Internet sites, our web site uses “cookies” in order to help your browser and our server provide you with better access to and service from our site. A “cookie” is a small file that a website’s server sends to your computer to allow the server to keep track of specific information about your session while you are connected to the site. Your computer will automatically destroy the cookie shortly after you close your browser. We do not use cookies to collect and maintain personal information about you. You can set your browser’s options to allow you to reject any unwanted cookies. Changes to this Policy We will post any changes to this privacy policy promptly on this page. If you have any questions, suggestions, or comments email us at
×
Glossary
